No Job's too big, no Pup's too small.
PAW Patrol: The Movie is a family, comedy,
adventure film directed by Cal Brunker.
Ryder and the pups are called to Adventure City to stop Mayor Humdinger
from turning the bustling metropolis into a state of chaos.
Gus (voice), played by Tyler Perry.
Humdinger / Turbot (voice), played by Ron Pardo.
Ryder (voice), played by Will Brisbin.
Marshall (Voice), played by Kingsley Marshall.
Rubble (voice), played by Keegan Hedley.
Chase (voice), played by Iain Armitage.
Paw Patrol: The Dino Movie is an upcoming Canadian animated action-adventure comedy
film based on the television series Paw Patrol created by Keith Chapman.
Produced by Spin Master Entertainment, it is the sequel to Paw Patrol: The Movie (2021) and Paw Patrol: The Mighty
Movie (2023) and is being directed by Cal Brunker, who co-wrote the screenplay with Bob Barlen.
The ensemble voice cast includes Mckenna Grace (voicing Skye), Jennifer Hudson, Fortune Feimster,
Snoop Dogg, Bill Nye, Meredith MacNeill, Paris Hilton, Terry Crews, and Jameela Jamil.
In September 2023, before the release of Paw Patrol: The Mighty Movie, Spin Master announced
a third Paw Patrol film is in development with a planned 2026 release date.
Returning crew members were announced soon after, including Brunker as a director
and Jennifer Dodge, Laura Clunie, and Toni Stevens as producers.
Mikros Image in Montreal, like its predecessors, returned to handle the animation, this time collaborating
in Paris, with the casting of Grace, Hudson and Feimster being announced the following year.
The film is based on the Dino Rescue sub-theme of the main show.
Paw Patrol: The Dino Movie is scheduled to be released in Canada by Elevation
Pictures and the United States by Paramount Pictures on August 14, 2026.
The film explores themes of cartoon, rescue mission, dog, animals, cartoon dog.
The tone is lighthearted.